His passion came with a price.
Caravaggio is a drama, history, romance film directed by Derek Jarman.
A retelling of the life of the celebrated 17th-century Baroque painter Michelangelo Merisi da Caravaggio
through his brilliant, nearly blasphemous paintings and his flirtations with the underworld.
Caravaggio, played by Nigel Terry.
Ranuccio, played by Sean Bean.
Davide, played by Garry Cooper.
Young Caravaggio, played by Dexter Fletcher.
Jerusaleme, played by Spencer Leigh.
Lena, played by Tilda Swinton.
Caravaggio is a 1986 British historical drama film directed by Derek Jarman.
The film is a fictionalised retelling of the life of Baroque
painter Michelangelo Merisi da Caravaggio.
The film explores themes of italy, artist,
painter, biography, male homosexuality.
The tone is emotional.